http://www.eoddata.com/about/privacy.aspx

The worlds #1 website for end of day & historical stock data
wide range of exchanges, data formats, tools and services
Main NavHOMEPRODUCTS & SERVICESHOW TOSUPPORTABOUTMY ACCOUNT
Sub NavAbout UsContact UsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyUseful LinksRegister
Privacy Policy
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how EODData treats personal information that EODData
collects and receives, including information related to your past use of
EODData products and services. Personal information is information about you
that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or
phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that EODData does not
own or control, or to people that EODData does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
EODData collects personal information when you register with EODData, when
you use EODData products or services, when you visit EODData pages or the pages of certain EODData
partners. EODData may combine information about you that we have with
information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address,
address, city, country, etc. Once you register with
EODData and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
EODData collects information about your transactions with us and with some of
our business partners, including information about your use of products and
services that we offer.
EODData automatically receives and records information on our server logs from
your browser, including your IP address, EODData cookie information, and the
page you request.
EODData uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the
advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for products and
services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide
anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
EODData does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with
other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services
you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following
circumstances:
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with
EODData under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your
personal information to help EODData communicate with you about offers from
EODData and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any
independent right to share this information.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or
exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate,
prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud,
situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person,
violations of EODData's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if EODData is acquired by or merged with
another company. In this event, EODData will notify you before information
about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
EODData displays targeted advertisements based on personal information.
Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who
interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for
example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
EODData does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you
interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an
ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the
assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
Cookies
EODData may set and access EODData cookies on your computer.
EODData lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set
and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their
cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or
other companies do not have access to EODData's cookies.
EODData uses web beacons to access EODData cookies inside and outside our
network of web sites and in connection with EODData products and services.
Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences
You can edit your EODData Account Information, including your preferences, at any time.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the
EODData service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and
the EODData Newsletter, that are considered part of your EODData account,
without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe
reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products
or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
Your EODData Account Information is password-protected.
In certain areas EODData uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data
transmissions.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
EODData may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes
in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary
email address specified in your EODData account or by placing a prominent
notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete our feedback form.
DOWNLOAD DATA
Download stock quote history quickly and easily in a variety of formats to suit your needs.
Exchange:
Winnipeg Commodity Exchange
Format:
Andromeda
ASCII (Intraday)
EzyCharts
FCharts
FCharts (Intraday)
MetaStock ASCII (7 column)
MetaStock ASCII (8 column)
Metastock ASCII (Intraday)
MetaStock ASCII with Names
Personal Stock Streamer
Quicken
SpiffyCharts
Spreadsheet (eg: Excel)
Windows on Wallstreet
Period:
Download all symbols
Date:
DOWNLOAD HISTORICAL DATA
Please select the Exchange and Format:
Exchange:
Winnipeg Commodity Exchange
Format:
Andromeda
ASCII (Intraday)
EzyCharts
FCharts
FCharts (Intraday)
MetaStock ASCII (7 column)
MetaStock ASCII (8 column)
Metastock ASCII (Intraday)
MetaStock ASCII with Names
Personal Stock Streamer
Quicken
SpiffyCharts
Spreadsheet (eg: Excel)
MEMBER LOGIN
Email/Username:
Password:
Daily Emails
Copyright © 2003-2020 EODData, LLC. All rights reserved.
Quotes are delayed at least 15 minutes. All information provided "as is" for informational purposes only, not intended for trading purposes or advice.
EODData will not be liable for any informational errors, incompleteness, or delays, or for any actions taken in reliance on information contained herein.
By accessing the EODData site, you agree not to redistribute the information found therein in any form without EODData's consent.
